A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1962-1963
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- General Files, 1962-1963
  - Preliminary Approval Forms (extra copies) 1962-1963 (Box 24)
  - Presidents Council 1962-1963 (Box 24)
  - Psychiatric Institute (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 24)
  - Psychology 1962-1963 (Box 24)
  - Public Occasions (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 24)
  - Public Relations 1962-1963 (Box 24)
  - Purchasing 1962-1963 (Box 24)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 24)
  - Questionnaires 1962-1963 (Box 24)
  - "R" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 24)
  - Radiation Protection 1962-1963 (Box 24)
  - Radio 1962-1963 (Box 24)
  - Raven Society 1962-1963 (Box 25)
  - Recommendations, Letters 1962-1963 (Box 25)
  - Registrar 1962-1963 (Box 25)
  - Registrar - Student Enrollment Report 1962-1963 (Box 25)
  - Religion 1962-1963 (Box 25)
  - Requisitions 1962-1963 (Box 25)
  - Requisitions - General Stores 1962-1963 (Box 25)
  - Research 1962-1963 (Box 25)
  - "Sa - Sl" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 25)
  - "Sm - Sz" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 25)
  - Salaries 1962-1963 (Box 26)
  - Senate, University 1962-1963 (Box 26)
  - Seven Society 1962-1963 (Box 26)
  - Sociology and Anthropology 1962-1963 (Box 26)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (see also Institutional Self-Study) 1962-1963 (Box 26)
  - Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges 1962-1963 (Box 26)
  - Southern Fellowship Fund (see also Council of Southern Universities) 1962-1963 (Box 26)
  - Southern Humanities Conference 1962-1963 (Box 26)
  - Southern Regional Education Board 1962-1963 (Box 26)
  - Southern University Conference 1962-1963 (Box 26)
  - Space Study (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 26)
  - Speech and Drama 1962-1963 (Box 26)
  - Speech - "The Bulwark of the Mind" (Final Day Address to the Graduating Class, University of Virginia, 9 June 1963), by Edgar F. Shannon, Jr. 1962-1963 (Box 27)
  - Speech - "To Make a Beginning" (Commencement Remarks at Mary Washington College, 2 June 1963), by Edgar F. Shannon, Jr. 1962-1963 (Box 27)
  - Speech - Edgar F. Shannon, Jr. to Division Superintendents, Virginia Public Schools, Roanoke, 11 March 1963 1962-1963 (Box 27)
  - Speech - "The University of Virginia in Northern Virginia," 1 March 1963 1962-1963 (Box 27)
  - Speeches and Articles 1962-1963 (Box 27)
  - State Board of Education 1962-1963 (Box 27)
  - State Council of Higher Education (see also Tax Study Commission) 1962-1963 (Box 28)
  - State Department of Education 1962-1963 (Box 28)
  - State Universities Association 1962-1963 (Box 28)
  - Statistics 1962-1963 (Box 28)
  - Student Affairs: July - December 1962 1962-1963 (Box 28)
  - Student Affairs: January - June 1963 1962-1963 (Box 28)
  - Student Aid and Placement 1962-1963 (Box 28)
  - Student Council 1962-1963 (Box 29)
  - Student Health Department (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 29)
  - Summer Session 1962-1963 (Box 29)
  - "T" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 29)
  - Tax Study Commission 1962-1963 (Box 29)
  - Taylor, Harry - Memorial 1962-1963 (Box 29)
  - Topics, University of Virginia 1962-1963 (Box 29)
  - Traffic Control 1962-1963 (Box 29)
  - Travel 1962-1963 (Box 29)
  - "U" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 29)
  - U. S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare 1962-1963 (Box 29)
  - U. S. Department of State 1962-1963 (Box 29)
  - U. S. Naval Academy 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Houses 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Allan, Dr. J. H. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Archer, Dr. V. W. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Beams, J. W. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Bowers, Fredson 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Boyd, T. M. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Burton, Dr. E. W. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Caplin, M. M. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Carriere, J. M. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Cherry, Ralph W. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Cowen, M. L. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Davis, A. K., Jr. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Dillard, H. C. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Egger, Rowland 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Forbes, J. D. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Geldard, F. A. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Gwathmey, A. T. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Gwathmey, Mrs. Roberta Hollingsworth 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Hart, James 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Leavell, Ullin W. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - McCasland, S. V. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Mayo, Bernard 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Molyneaux, Lambert 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Moran, C. E. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Mulholland, Dr. H. B. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Nash, C. F. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Singleton, R. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Spencer, Hugh 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Stevenson, E. C. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Vaughan, J. L. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Vining, D. H. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Waddell, W. W. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Whyburn, G. T. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Wilson, George P. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Woodward, F. D. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Woody, T. B. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Housing Applications - Younger, E. E. 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Center in Virginia 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Hall (see also Field House) 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Press of Virginia (see also Virginia University Press) 1962-1963 (Box 30)
  - University Printing Office 1962-1963 (Box 31)
  - "V" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 31)
  - Virginia Academy of Science (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 31)
  - Virginia Associated Research Center (see Special Permanent File) (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 31)
  - Virginia Junior Academy of Science (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 31)
  - Virginia Education Association 1962-1963 (Box 31)
  - Virginia Foundation for Independent Colleges 1962-1963 (Box 31)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1962-1963 (Box 31)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1962-1963 (Box 31)
  - Virginia University Press (see also University Press of Virginia Committee) 1962-1963 (Box 31)
  - Visitors - Board Committees 1962-1963 (Box 31)
  - Visitors - Board Executive Committee 1962-1963 (Box 31)
  - Visitors - General 1962-1963 (Box 31)
  - Visitors - Docket and Minutes, 7 June 1963 1962-1963 (Box 31)
  - Visitors - Docket and Minutes, 20 April 1963 1962-1963 (Box 32)
  - Visitors - Docket and Minutes, 9 February 1963 1962-1963 (Box 32)
  - Visitors - Docket and Minutes, 8 December 1963 1962-1963 (Box 32)
  - Visitors - Docket and Minutes, 29 September 1962 1962-1963 (Box 32)
  - Visitors - Hartfield, Col. Joseph M. 1962-1963 (Box 33)
  - Visitors - Berkeley, Mr. Norborne 1962-1963 (Box 33)
  - Visitors - Pollock, Dr. Herbert C. 1962-1963 (Box 33)
  - Visitors - "Wa - Wh" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 33)
  - Visitors - "Wi - Wz" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 33)
  - Visitors - Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies 1962-1963 (Box 33)
  - Visitors - Women, Dean of 1962-1963 (Box 33)
  - Visitors - "X - Y - Z" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 33)
  - Visitors - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) 1962-1963 (Box 33)